The Buffalo Bills select linebacker TJ
Parker from Clemson.
>> TJ Parker, welcome to Buffalo. The Bills
select you with the 35th overall pick.
When Buffalo called your name last
night, you told head coach Joe Brady,
"I'm ready to hunt." How will you hunt
in your rookie season?
>> Man, that's just me being and doing
whatever I can. Um, you know, we have a
great veteran group. Uh, guys like
Bradley Chub and Oliver, Greg Russo. I'm
gonna get to those guys and try to learn
from them as much as possible and and
and compete. You know what I'm saying?
Come in, be a great teammate, and like I
said, hunt whatever it takes to do to
win, whether that's special teams, you
know, get on the field, do whatever it
takes, hunt. I'm I'm a dog, so I got I
got to eat. So, whatever that takes,
just having that mentality, man, I can't
wait and I'm excited. So,
>> what's one draft night memory that you
won't ever forget?
Um, just seeing my parents' excitement,
you know, when I first got the call, my
heart was racing to the point where you
can feel my heartbeat on my arms and I
was, as soon as I got the call, I was
stunned. I mean, I didn't really know to
say it. Kind of was just shocked and
just just trying to be in the moment.
And to see my parents just jump for joy
and just be excited that I'm going to
Buffalo. Um, it really meant the world
to me.
>> Speed to power is your game. You have
violent hands that wear out an opposing
offense. You said, "I want to put the
pain on somebody." Where will your skill
set show up most in Buffalo?
>> Uh definitely in the run, you know, and
in the pass game as well, but um for me,
I'm a physical player who who doesn't
shy away from contact. You know, I try
to put my body on on somebody else on
the offense every play I get, you know
what I'm saying? And over time, that
wears them down like you said. U you
know, I want my opponent to to lead the
game knowing that that TJ Parker was on
their head all night. Um and regardless
of what they got to do, um you know, for
me, that's just how I love playing the
game. Very physical and violent.
contact and being physical. It It hurts.
You have to be willing to do it. Where
did you learn that I'm okay with this
pain and I want to inflict it on you?
>> Since four years old, you know, me and
my brother used to rough house all the
time. I love WWE as a kid. So, just
trying those moves out. You get to you
build the callus up of of getting bumps
and bruises. When I told my mom I want
to play football at four years old, I
said I want to hit somebody and she
threw me right into football. And I
loved it. I get to fly around, hit
people as hard as I can, and there's no
consequence to it. So from there, I just
knew I love the game. So that's where
that comes from.
>> Asking to play football at four years
old, do you have an obvious love and
passion for the game? Where does that
show up on the field most?
>> Uh, every play. Um, for me, I love it.
Um, it's my it's my safe space where,
you know, anything you dealing with, you
can go football and know he'll be right
there with you. Um, at 4 years old, I
loved watching JJ Watt play. You know
what I'm saying? as a kid, you know, you
grew up in Texas playing little league
football, you know, all everybody talks
about a Texans. Um, and just seeing how
he played the game was just so violent
and it was just unbelievable. So, for
me, it was just like it was a passion.
>> Your pass rush moves are unique. You
love to grab hands and rip. You don't
see a lot of other pass rushers as
effective as you are doing something
like that. Where did you pick up some of
those moves?
>> Um, for me, it came from my high school
coach, Adrien Laos. Um, man, I met him
in in the seventh grade and we've been
working and training just to really
understand how to pass rush and how to
play defensive end in general. Um, and
it kind of just helped me correlate my
game um and understand what I need to do
and just over time like you said just
different pass grabbing wrist and hands
and things like that. I think it just
came natural just something I I did but
didn't really try to do and then over
time I just started working it and
working it. Um, and it became a skill
that I learned um and it became very
effective for me.
>> General manager Brandon Bean called you
a three-own player. you played in 39
straight games, a very durable player.
What type of routine did you have to be
so durable throughout the season?
>> Um, for me it's just it's about, you
know, um, taking care of your body.
That's the biggest thing. Prehab and
then post-workout or postgame or
whatever. Um, and I early on, you know,
I kind of understood what I needed to
do. Um, but Clemson does a great job of
bringing back their their league guys
and their vets and they come and train
there. um really seeing how they treat
their body, how they come in hours
before the workout, taking care of their
body, stretching, warming up, hot tub,
cold tub, whatever they do. And even
afterwards, um it really opened my eyes
like, man, I'm trying to get to, you
know, where they're at. Cuz you got guys
like Christian Wilkins, Dexter, you
know, um making hundreds of millions of
dollars. Um whereas and I'm trying to
get there at one point. So if they're
doing it, I should be doing it as well.
Um and then over time as I'm growing, I
see what works for me and I kind of
implement it that way. Um and really,
you know, just building that great
schedule as I got older, it really
helped me. uh you know play a lot longer
and then recover a lot faster. So
>> 41 and a half tackles for loss in 39
games. You get after it when you're in
the game in terms of getting after the
quarterback. What are you thinking every
rep,
>> man? It's like you don't even know how
to explain it. You just know when when
it's time to rush the passer, it's like
it's like a dog staring at a toy. You
know what I'm saying? You know exactly
what you want and you can't you got to
have it. Um for me, it's like my eyes
get real big and I know what time it is.
It's like a different mode when you know
you get to rush the passer um and get a
sack because after you make the play,
you know, you hear the crowd cheering,
you see teammates celebrating with you
and like that's the moment you try to
chase. So,
>> you come from a military family. Your
dad was in the army. How does that
lifestyle set you up for the NFL?
>> Um for me, you know, just creating great
balance and structure. You know, my dad
was always uh somebody, you know, who
who had a great structure around him,
great people around him, and you know,
he taught me a lot of values when it
comes to how I treat people and how to
represent yourself. My dad always told
me the greatest thing I'm going to give
you is your last name. Don't do nothing
to ruin it. Um, so at an early age, I
knew to treat everybody with respect and
to go about my way in a mature manner.
Um, and it really helped me, you know,
make a lot of great decisions in my
life. Um, and then, you know, translate
to football field.
>> Did you do any crazy military workouts
growing up? any any like five minute
wall sits or anything like that that we
can expect from you?
>> We had a we had a couple of them wall
sits uh for sure. I ain't going to get
into too much detail, but just know like
you know we we was well we was good kids
you know uh my dad you know he ain't
pushed the workouts on us too early but
as I started getting older we did a lot
of a lot of tire pushes, a lot of flips
and stuff like that in the yard. A lot
of carries. Um so it was definitely
helpful for my football career. What are
three words that best describe TJ
Parker's personality?
>> Uh, funny.
Um,
um, spontaneous,
uh, and loving.
>> What's one thing that most people don't
know about you?
>> I know HOW TO SEW.
>> OH,
>> YEAH. My mom was a seamress and she
modeled for 20 years. So, she taught me
how to sew. So, like if I had to fix up
jeans or I can make my own hoodie. It's
crazy. Um, when I was committing to
Clemson, I took Tapestry blankets out of
Clemson material and I made my own
hoodie. Um, and I wore it when Coach
Swinny came and ate breakfast and stuff
with us. I still have it. Um, it's in my
closet somewhere. Um, but yeah, I know
to sew.
>> Okay, we're going to have a TJ Parker
brand later on in life where where
you're sewing in your free time,
releasing merch for Bills fans.
>> Hey, eventually eventually once I get
settled in, we can make something like
that work.
>> Let's go rapid fire here. What's your
favorite hobby?
>> The golf.
>> What are you best at?
My favorite club is a seven iron, but
other than that, you know what I'm
saying? I can hit the ball consistently.
That's it. I ain't saying I'm good. I
ain't saying to go straight,
>> but I can hit the ball. That's all that
matters. It's peaceful.
>> Consistently is really good in the game
of golf. Some people really struggle
with consistency.
>> Yeah. And it it teaches you how to be
calm because you can't be mad at nobody
but yourself. So,
>> what's on the pregame playlist?
>> Oh, NBA Young Boy.
>> What's on your pregame routine? Do you
do anything crazy?
Um, I drink a Red Bull right before the
game and I hate the smelling salts. They
get me going.
>> Red Bull and smelling salts.
>> Yeah.
>> Describes the dog that you are, how you
get into the game and how you want to
hunt.
>> Yeah, for sure. It It act It activates
me right before I go out and I just turn
into a different person. So,
>> are you slamming the Red Bull or are you
drinking it over over some time?
>> Oh, no. I'm chugging it. I'm chugging.
>> We're chugging it. Yeah. What's your
favorite food?
>> Uh, chicken.
>> Chicken. How do you like it cooked?
>> Uh, I like it roasted. oven roasted.
>> And finally, what's one thing you want
to tell Bill's Mafia? You can look into
the camera right there.
>> Bill's Mafia, you guys are getting a
dog. Somebody I'm going to do whatever
it takes to win so you guys can be
satisfied and I'm in the fight with
y'all and I love y'all.
>> TJ Parker, welcome to Buffalo. That blue
looks good on you, man. We're happy to
have you here.
>> I'm happy to be here and I can't wait to
get going.